TAP version 13
# Subtest: customer checkout is responsive, ephemeral, accessible, and bound to server-issued shipping
ok 1 - customer checkout is responsive, ephemeral, accessible, and bound to server-issued shipping
  ---
  duration_ms: 25399.3161
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: shipping quote proxy preserves exact origin, body, and only a bounded customer projection
ok 2 - shipping quote proxy preserves exact origin, body, and only a bounded customer projection
  ---
  duration_ms: 15.323
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: commerce POST proxies fail closed for wrong origins, oversized bodies, upstream failures, and malformed authority
ok 3 - commerce POST proxies fail closed for wrong origins, oversized bodies, upstream failures, and malformed authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.0336
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout proxy accepts only a Stripe TEST URL and never returns extra upstream fields
ok 4 - checkout proxy accepts only a Stripe TEST URL and never returns extra upstream fields
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1157
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout source keeps delivery ephemeral and derives totals and gates from server responses
ok 5 - checkout source keeps delivery ephemeral and derives totals and gates from server responses
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.0159
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
ok 6 - scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.0751
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
ok 7 - checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
  ---
  duration_ms: 12534.5872
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..7
# tests 7
# suites 0
# pass 7
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 39231.558
