TAP version 13
# Subtest: shipping quote proxy preserves exact origin, body, and only a bounded customer projection
ok 1 - shipping quote proxy preserves exact origin, body, and only a bounded customer projection
  ---
  duration_ms: 16.3352
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: commerce POST proxies fail closed for wrong origins, oversized bodies, upstream failures, and malformed authority
ok 2 - commerce POST proxies fail closed for wrong origins, oversized bodies, upstream failures, and malformed authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.1414
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout proxy accepts only a Stripe TEST URL and never returns extra upstream fields
ok 3 - checkout proxy accepts only a Stripe TEST URL and never returns extra upstream fields
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1309
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout source keeps delivery ephemeral and derives totals and gates from server responses
ok 4 - checkout source keeps delivery ephemeral and derives totals and gates from server responses
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.2537
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: safe order-status proxy requires one opaque TEST Session and cannot enumerate orders
ok 5 - safe order-status proxy requires one opaque TEST Session and cannot enumerate orders
  ---
  duration_ms: 16.9718
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: status normalization exposes only bounded payment state and rejects provider internals
ok 6 - status normalization exposes only bounded payment state and rejects provider internals
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3083
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: success page checks the server projection and never treats the query string as payment authority
ok 7 - success page checks the server projection and never treats the query string as payment authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.4622
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal configuration normalization exposes only browser-safe state
ok 8 - PayPal configuration normalization exposes only browser-safe state
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0847
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal create, capture, and status projections reject provider extras
ok 9 - PayPal create, capture, and status projections reject provider extras
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4251
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal POST proxy enforces Public origin and forwards only the bounded request
ok 10 - PayPal POST proxy enforces Public origin and forwards only the bounded request
  ---
  duration_ms: 17.2761
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
ok 11 - scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.0666
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
ok 12 - checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
  ---
  duration_ms: 8063.7582
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..12
# tests 12
# suites 0
# pass 12
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 9105.3522
