TAP version 13
# Subtest: PayPal configuration normalization exposes only browser-safe state
ok 1 - PayPal configuration normalization exposes only browser-safe state
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1392
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal create, capture, and status projections reject provider extras
ok 2 - PayPal create, capture, and status projections reject provider extras
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4217
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal POST proxy enforces Public origin and forwards only the bounded request
ok 3 - PayPal POST proxy enforces Public origin and forwards only the bounded request
  ---
  duration_ms: 15.432
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
ok 4 - scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.6185
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
ok 5 - checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
  ---
  duration_ms: 8486.1277
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..5
# tests 5
# suites 0
# pass 5
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 9208.0865
