TAP version 13
# Subtest: scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
ok 1 - scoped Public projection excludes extra fields and removes merchant contact below threshold
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.9294
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
ok 2 - checkout agreement is explicit, correctable and private at 1440, 768 and 390
  ---
  duration_ms: 8181.2821
  type: 'test'
  ...
# (node:21160) ExperimentalWarning: Type Stripping is an experimental feature and might change at any time
# (Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
# Subtest: retained server agreement policies match the actual Public policy versions and full text
ok 3 - retained server agreement policies match the actual Public policy versions and full text
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.6681
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..3
# tests 3
# suites 0
# pass 3
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 8937.5837
